For political prisoner George Jackson, revolution was
not a choice... it was a necessity
Black August is a drama film directed by Samm Styles.
The last 14 months of George Jackson's life was an existence under subjective and
objective conditions in California's industrial prison complex.
George Jackson would spend 11 years in jail (7 of which were in solitary
confinement) for a $70 gas station robbery crime in 1960.
He was 18 years of age when the sentence of one
year-to-life was handed down to him.
George Jackson, played by Gary Dourdan.
David Dryer, played by Darren Bridgett.
Jonathan Jackson, played by Ezra J. Stanley.
Lumumba, played by 'Big' LeRoy Mobley.
Georgia Jackson, played by Vonetta McGee.
FBI Agent Walker, played by Don Williams.
Black August is a 2007 drama film directed by Samm Styles and starring Gary Dourdan,
Darren Bridgett, Ezra Stanley, "Big" Leroy Mobley, and Don Williams.
It was produced by Tcinque Sampson.
The film centers on the story of George Jackson's life.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.